{
    "subject": "resource/Ken_Gillespie",
    "predicate": "property/dateOfBirth",
    "object": "1952-06-28",
    "human_readable": "Ken Gillespie was born on June 28, 1952.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9625818133354187,
            "question": "What does June 28th, 1952 represent for Ken Gillespie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8755213022232056,
            "question": "Is June the month Ken Gillespie was born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8744826912879944,
            "question": "When was Ken Gillespie born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7641285061836243,
            "question": "On which day of the month was Ken Gillespie born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7532259225845337,
            "question": "What is Ken Gillespie's birth date?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6971797943115234,
            "question": "What month and day was Ken Gillespie born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.503066897392273,
            "question": "How many years have passed since Ken Gillespie's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44543686509132385,
            "question": "In what year did Ken Gillespie come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.444146990776062,
            "question": "What is Ken Gillespie's birthdate in numerical format?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3899044990539551,
            "question": "If today is July 1st, 2023, how old is Ken Gillespie?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ken Gillespie was born on June 28, 1952.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2459_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Ken Gillespie's birthdate in numerical format?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2459_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Ken Gillespie come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2459_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How many years have passed since Ken Gillespie's birth?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2459_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2459_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2459_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2459_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2459_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2459_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2459_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2459_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2459_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2459_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2459_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Ken Gillespie was born on June 28, 1952. This is stated explicitly in both files with path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2459/re-ranker-msmarco/103.txt and /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2459/re-ranker-msmarco/97.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe document states \"Ken Gillespie was born on June 28, 1952,\" which directly supports the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}